My Lord Count Zebron, Countess Raffia, and Count Olga, my gratitude to all of you for allowing me to intrude on your time.
Our condolences to you for your loss, Count Troyard.
Most regrettable and quite tragic.
Yes.
I was very greatly indebted to your late father, the Count. Any assistance in my power to render is yours.
Thank you, that is most kind. And with that being said, now is not the time to wallow in sentiment.
Most commendable of you.
This is the time when all the Orbital Knights should come together and continue with our invasion of the Earth.
For Count Sosbohm, that is the finest way we can commemorate him.
Right. Everyone among us should sail forward all in pursuit of our goal.
I see now.
Really? And you intend your hand to be on the helm?
If I may be so bold.
Hmm. By the by, I understand you will be dueling Count Morissian.
I find it unsettling to be fighting at a time we should unite.
Don't you agree, my Lord Count Troyard?
It seems that no Terran, no lowly Terran, could ever stand against the mighty verse.
Such an assumption creates an opening, which then becomes a tear, and soon after that, a huge hole.
And then it disintegrates.
This is the state of the Orbital Knights.
Now you have gone too far, Count Troyard.
As you know, I do not have the advantage of being verse-born.
However, as an outsider, I do have a clear perspective.
Now this upcoming duel is the result of hubris in a night, and I think it is my duty to point out his mistake.
Yes, I see. You do have a point.
But Count Olga!
Loath as I am to admit this, it is truth nonetheless. Some portion of it at least.
I must trust in your discretion, Count Troyard.
Your attack was magnificent against their trident base.
Count Zebran, Countess Rathia, you have done me great honor.
In hearing me out, I am in your debt.
I am in your debt.
Captain, all cruise missiles appear to have been intercepted.
Looks like a saturation attack isn't going to work.
Data says a cataphrac is scorching Solas, and the pilot is Count Selnakis.
Its beam weapon is effective as far as a satellite belt, meaning air support is too vulnerable to be helpful.
It is quite the monster.
Message from assault team.
They're about to make landfall.
Launch more cruise missiles.
Let's keep his eyes on us.
Looks like up close and personal is how we're going to have to do it.
Let's do this.
All right, all pilots up and ready to launch.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, nothing.
Say, Raiye.
Yeah?
The other day, there was that manhunt all of a sudden.
It was for, um, ma, ma, ma, ma...
Count Mazurek.
Right.
How do you suppose he got away?
Don't know.
I wonder if Inahu knows anything.
Why would he?
He interrogated him.
Did he say anything to you?
Not a word.
It's time to launch.
Let's go.
All right.
Inko, I'm sorry.
To think such a simple mechanism can show one's bearings.
Of course, only on a planet with magnetic poles.
Now then, we have Count Troyard and Inaho Kaizuka.
Both of them are sons of the Earth.
Can either be trusted?
It's so simple, one cannot go astray, right?
Like many things.
Are you truly going to go out and fight this duel, Slain?
Yes.
I have been challenged, so I cannot back down.
This is my fault, isn't it?
Because I allowed Count Morilcion's visit.
Not at all.
Rather, I have you to thank for it.
It is the perfect opportunity to demonstrate my strengths.
If I am a victor in this duel,
it will be a deterrent to the orbital knights who oppose me.
There's nothing to be concerned about.
Then your dream might actually become reality someday.
I don't have a dream.
A lowly Terran now holds genuine power within verse.
I have felt it, ever since the very first time we met,
that the two of us were quite similar in some way.
Do you intend to hold your grudge against the royal family forever?
Yes.
How deliciously satisfying to see someone without a drop of Vercyan blood gaining power.
And I think that you will never let go either of a Salem.
You truly love her, don't you?
Slain, if you were to allow it, I would like to give you my help.
Even if I am to be my sister's substitute.
All platoons, report.
Belgian platoon, positioned.
Marimano platoon, positioned.
Potok platoon, positioned.
Wokai platoon, positioned.
Mustang platoon, in position.
There's no way around that beam weapon he's got out there.
If he sees you, it'll be goodbye.
Commence operation.
A smokescreen that scatters everything from infrared to radar waves.
They think they're smart.
What the hell?
Prepare to die.
Blessdale leader to all platoons.
Move out.
To the south bank now.
Fire that smoke.
You waste your time.
Fire, fire, fire!
Get his attention focused on us.
And don't get hit.
How are we going to keep his attention and not get ourselves shot to pieces?
Where is now?
All right, we're here.
Be careful now.
I'm here.
Okay, I'm patching you in.
Acoustic analysis.
Enemy coordinates.
Target is at...
29.9511.
By minus...
90.0855.
Roger that.
Targeting location.
Fire.
Firing.
Roger.
Counting down.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
What are they doing?
Impact.
Correct by...
037-025.
It came from the sea.
And fire.
Cannon fire from a ship?
Oh, that was close.
The effect of a beam weapon is that it can only travel in a straight line.
If we're below the curvature of the Earth, we should be safe.
On the other hand, since our artillery shells follow a parabola due to Earth's gravity,
we can curb our shots over the horizon.
As long as we can locate the target.
Correct by...
283.
Minus 472.
High-speed rounds!
Now fire!
How can they be targeting me so accurately?
They don't even have observation satellites.
So that's it!
Captain, the UAVs relaying our laser comms have all been taken out!
We can't communicate with Ensign Kaiska!
Raiye.
Go to tracer rounds.
Fire exactly as I say.
There.
No!
Bastard!
Tracer rounds, ma'am!
Do you seriously think you can bring down my solace from that far?
Yuki, get yourself clear!
Fire!
Lord, Officer Kaiska!
No, stay back!
Aw, crap!
Second burst!
And a third!
Correct.
By 00203.
And fire!
Kaiska!
That's it.
Just stand there and act all smug.
Now you shall be reduced to ash by my scorching light!
Go ahead and shoot, you frog-faced bastard!
Yuki, I'm okay.
I only lost an arm.
What about you?
We're fine.
Ensign Kaiska is safe.
That's great news.
No, it's not.
I told you to get yourself clear.
You disobeyed an order, Warrant Officer.
Hey, don't even think you're superior to me just because of your higher rank.
I am your superior.
Big sisters aren't allowed to be ordered around by their little brothers.
Clisdale leader to all platoons.
Mission complete.
Let's return to base.
These bloom down on Earth.
They are called roses.
Is there something bothering you?
Are you certain that you want to fight this duel, my lord slain?
I have been forced to fight for my life many times before.
But if you...
Do you worry about me, Adele Ritzo?
Thank you for that.
It used to be that you would just glare at me.
But things were different then.
Roses have a lot of meanings in the language of flowers.
Red roses mean romance and love.
While blue roses mean miracle.
Miracle.
But blue roses also have another meaning.
And that meaning...
Well, it just might be true.
Let's get this over with.
Herschel, launch!
My lord slain, may you be victorious.
Thorsus, launch!
The sight of a lowborn dog putting on airs is offensive to me.
On the honor of the Verse Orbital Knights, I shall exact my punishment.
Attempting to seize an official post from Avarice, and not just cause, is an insult to public order.
As the one charged with the safety of her highness, I shall punish you.
This will be a duel between Orbital Knights, Count Marilsian, and Count Troyard.
Begin!
The rumors were right, you are a slippery one.
But are you able to escape my Herschel's multiple attacks?
To be careful, my lord!
With your predictions or not, you cannot defend against this kind of firepower.
Careful my lord with your predictions or not you cannot defend against this kind of firepower
What seems you're fairly clever after all nevertheless
You told you don't your efforts of you know
In the language of flowers blue roses mean miracle
But they have another meaning as well the impossible
Is there no chance is it beyond reason to hope
Is there not even the smallest chance you will ever wake up again
Please
Give us a miracle
So
It did mean impossible
I believe in you
There are no miracles for me
Is running the only thing you can do fight you inferior scum
You know what are you watching out here they're fighting each other, huh?
You know what are you watching out here?
They're fighting each other, huh?
Huh?
Where?
Nowhere left for you to run
You are the one who has nowhere to go
Huh?
Where?
Nowhere left for you to run
You are the one who has nowhere to go
Huh?
The Herschel strength is a simultaneous attack from all directions
But here in this tunnel your attack was confined to just one direction
Material loading tunnels for the moon base's construction
I've mapped their locations
I will not be defeated
By the likes of you
The Herschel strength is a simultaneous attack from all directions
But here in this tunnel your attack was confined to just one direction
Material loading tunnels for the moon base's construction
I've mapped their locations
I will not be defeated
By the likes of you
You are nothing, scum
The winner
Count Slain Troyard
In accordance with the noble law of the Empire of Verse
All of Count Marilsion's assets are to be treasured
These assets are to be transferred to Count Slain Sosbaum Troyard. Do you object?
I... Count Baro Cruz officially certify these results.
It's over.
You can see everything, can't you, Inaho?
Yes.
Except... what I really want to know. That I can't see.
I'm sorry, Yinko.
I didn't want to get you involved.
You jerk.
Thank you very much.
Just better for you.
There are people who do there seem to be influences in them.
How do you understand the story of Heaven now?
Didn't even know why we are in it, table.
You have 2 answers.
In conclusion, I wish to inform you, the 37 clans, of the new policy that we shall put into place.
We, who have paid in blood to acquire these new lands, on the earth, no longer need to rely on our homeworld.
Children eventually grow up, and they must leave their mother's protection and strike out on their own.
And so I, a Salem vs. Ellusia, shall take count slain Sazbom Troyard for my husband.
And I now proclaim a new kingdom, here, in Earth-space.
Let's go.
Ah
We don't know too many powers
You are too lucky
I don't know if you knew, but I always admired you.
You were beautiful, you were kind-hearted, and beloved by all.
You had all the things that I did not.
But you and I have one thing in common, sister.
One very special thing.
Royal blood. The old Noah activation factor.
A power that Slane needs right now.
I have decided that Slane is the partner I need, and as for him, he has chosen me as well.
So going forward, I am now a Salem vs. Elusia.
I am you.
So you can let go, sister.
Not just yet.
You may be only a puppet, but you are still my sister.
Pleasant dreams.
Let's have a look at this.
You may be only a puppet.
Let's see in the next.
To be a fanfare.
And we'll be a